

#### **CAREER SUMMARY**

I'm a dedicated and experienced telecommunication engineer within a total 16 years of experience of which 10 years in GSM and 6 years in fixed networks. In 1990 I fell in love with seeing a PC for the first time in my life. Here my passion for the IT industry began and so I've started my career in technical support in telecom. I was a specialist in PC hardware, designing, layout making, and system administrating.

In 2020 I've decided to gain new skills and boost my career joining the training for Front-End Developing in the IT school INTEC Brussels. Currently, I'm looking for opportunities where I can further upgrade my programming skills and new horizons open up for me in the area of Front-End and possibly BackEnd development.

#### **HOW TO CONTACT ME**

Address: Dieweg 34A, 1180 UCCLE Phone: (+32) 473-26-96-23 Email: denpla@gmail.com

#### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- Platform, telecom & network troubleshooting.
- System administration.
- Front-End Developing.

Platforms: MSC (Mobile Switching Center) Alcatel 1000 System 12, Alcatel System 12 fixed, 9120 BSC, 9130 BSC&MFS, 9100 BTS, 9153 OMCR&NPO, SUN, HP, CISCO.

**Equipment:** Alcatel-Lucent, Nokia, SUN, HP, Cisco, Tektronix, Ericsson, Powerware.

## DENIS PLAKSIYCHUK

TELECOM TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER & JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Front-End Developing course**

#### **INTEC BRUSSELS | 2020**

 Full-time intense course of HTML, CSS, Javascript and modern applications for Front-End Developing using also such popular Javascript frameworks as VUE and React.

#### **Technical Support Engineer**

#### Penta Consulting | 2019

- Technical support and troubleshooting of Alcatel-Lucent OMCR for customer Etisalat (Sri Lanka).
- Technical support and troubleshooting of Alcatel-Lucent OMCR and BSC MX equipment for customer Getesa (Equatorial Guinea).
- Work on service deck system of Penta Consulting.

#### **Technical Support Engineer Alcatel S12 Level3**

#### Proximus Belgium & Penta Consulting | 2018

- Technical support and troubleshooting of Alcatel-Lucent S12 fixed exchanges in the frame of maintenance contract with Proximus company group in Belgium.
- Work on service deck system of Penta Consulting.

#### **Technical Support Engineer Alcatel S12 Level2 & OLO**

#### Proximus Belgium, Nokia & Penta Consulting | 2012-2018

- Technical support and troubleshooting of Alcatel-Lucent S12 fixed exchanges in Belgium for Proximus company group as the subcontractor from Nokia and Penta Consulting including on-call duty.
- Troubleshooting for Other Local Operators (OLO) interconnect project.
- Work on service deck system of Proximus.

## Technical Support Engineer at Moscow Technical Support Organization

### Alcatel-Lucent Moscow | 2003 - 2012

• Technical support and troubleshooting Level2/3 of Alcatel-Lucent S12 mobile exchanges in Russia for many of major customers.

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Operating Systems: Windows, SUN Solaris 9/10, HP-UX 11, LINUX.

Network Protocols: CCS N7, TCP/IP stack.

Software: Alcatel-Lucent SMA, SMC-CMC, OMCR, Tektronix K1297/K15 protocol tester software, OSIX, VMware, Visual Studio Code.

Databases: Relational database S12, Oracle 9i SQL&PL/SQL(basic), Firebase.

Programming Languages: S12 MPTMON script language (multiprocessor test monitor), Unix bash, HTML, CSS, Javascript.

#### SOFT SKILLS

- · Good problem-solving skills.
- Sociable and kind.
- Both team player and able to work on my own.
- Quick learner and always ready to master new skills.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Russian: Native

English: Full professional proficiency French: Limited working proficiency

Dutch: Elementary

#### **PERSONAL**

Date of birth: 13.06.1974

Driving license: Available (cat. B)

Marital status: Married.

Children: Two children 12 and 15

years old.

#### PERSONAL REFERENCES

Aminash Patel - Executive Director Penta Consulting aminashpatel@pentaconsulting.com (+44) 208-25-47-449 (+44) 774-88-335-44

#### Sergey Garchenko -

Business Operations Manager Nokia sergey\_garchenko@hotmail.com +(31) 651-22-04-24

#### Noortje De Cleene

Jobcoach noortje.decleene@intecbrussel.be 02 411-29-07

- Technical support and troubleshooting of Alcatel-Lucent OMCR and BSC equipment.
- Technical support and troubleshooting of ALcatel SMC/CMC for S12.
- On-call duty for all lines of supporting products.
- Test products and features in laboratory.
- Work on service deck system of Alcatel-Lucent.

## **Network Engineer and System Administrator**

#### Apostrof TS Moscow | 2002 - 2003

- Server administration based on Microsoft server solutions.
- Network and security administration.
- New installations enrollment and purchasing new equipment.
- User technical support.

#### **Project Engineer**

## TAIF-Radiotelecommunication Ink, TAIF-Intelset Ink. Kazan | 2000- 2002

- Design and implementation of the network projects at group of TAIF company.
- Customers support.
- PABX Ericsson MD110 and Business Phone commissioning.
- Powerware On-line UPS 60kVa installation.

### **Technical Support Specialist**

# CIVT KSU (The Center of Computer Techniques in the Kazan State University) | Jan 1997 - Nov 2000

- Design and implementation network projects at Kazan State University.
- Installation and administration the network infrastructure.
- Introduction to the Network Technologies lectures (KSU developed) for various customers.

#### **EDUCATION AND KEY CERTIFICATES**

#### **Kazan State University (KSU) Russia**

Applied Mathematics | Kazan 1991-1996 Master's degree.

SCSA Sun Certified System Administrator Solaris9 (2007) SCNA Sun Certified Network Administrator Solaris9 (2007)

Oracle 9i SQL&PL/SQL basics (2008)

Alcatel 1360 SMC 3. 2.2, Workshop for TAC Engineers (2005)

Alcatel 1360 SMC 3.2.2, OAM for TAC Engineers (2005)

Alcatel 1000 S12 WR. 1A Advanced maintenance Engineer (2004)

Alcatel 1000 S12 MSC GSM, O&M Engineer (2003)

Alcatel 8338/60 HLR, O&M Engineer (2003)

Alcatel 1000 S12 IN-Handling on SSP (2003)

Alcatel 1000 S12 AMADEUS Application (2003)

Ericsson (MD110 BC10 Implement & manage) (2000)

Ericsson (BP 50/250 Implement & manage) (2000)

Powerware UPS installer/engineer Prime/Profile up to 60kVA (2000)

From 2010 till 2012 I've passed the training for Alcatel-Lucent BSS equipment: 9100 BTS, 9130 BSC&MFS MX, 9153 OMCR&NPO and also NRS1 (Network routing specialist) exam preparation and LTE including the introduction to SR 7750 equipment in Alcatel University Moscow.